Guide to the Douglass Cecil North Papers, 1942-2012 and undated RL.00955
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Conferences and Seminars, 1963-2012; 2
  - 1984 July 28-Aug. 18, Conference on Rationality and Collective Action (Box 25)
  - 1984 Aug. 15-17, Nobel Symposium: "Growth of Government" (Box 25)
  - 1984 Aug., Bellagio and Nobel Conferences (Box 25)
  - 1984 Aug. Rose, Richard: "The State's Contribution to the Welfare Mix" (Box 25)
  - 1984 Sept. 7-15, Conference on Markets and History (Box 25)
  - 1984 Sept. 9-13, Liberty Fund symposium: "Freedom and the History of Markets" (Box 25)
  - 1984 Sept. 21-22, Economic History Association meeting (Box 25)
  - 1984 Sept. Rose, Richard: "Dual Accountability in Public Organisations" (Box 25)
  - 1984 Oct. 22, Asociacion Argentina De Historia Economica: Annual Meeting (Box 25)
  - 1985 Jan. 17-20, American Liberty and Modern Republics, Houston, Texas (Box 25)
  - 1985 Feb. 6, Mancur Olson lecture at Washington University (Box 25)
  - 1985 Feb. 12, "The Economy's Evolution and Its Effects on Work," Meramec College (Box 25)
  - 1985 Feb. 21-23, Public Choice Society Annual Meeting, New Orleans (Box 25)
  - 1985 Mar. 28-30, Rise and Decline of Nations, University of Victoria (Box 25)
  - 1985 Apr. 12, Political Economy Seminar, Williams College (Box 25)
  - 1984 Apr. 26, Panel, Brown University: "Theoretical Perspectives on States and Markets" (Box 26)
  - 1985 May 11, Agency for International Development (AID) (Box 26)
  - 1985 June 12-14, International Seminar on the New Institutional Economics, Saarbrucken (Box 26)
  - 1985 July 15-20, The State in the New Political Economy: 13th IPSA World Congress, Paris (Box 26)
  - 1985 July The Athenaeum Conference (Box 26)
  - 1985 July The American Ditchey Foundation (Box 26)
  - 1985 Oct., Freedom and Liberty Conference, Washington University (Box 26)
  - 1985 Oct. 9, Economics Department at St. John's University Conferences and Seminars (Box 26)
  - 1985 Oct. 11, "The Rise of Merchant Empires," University of Minnesota (Box 26)
  - 1985 Oct. 24-26, Liberty Fund Conference, Washington University, St. Louis (Box 26)
  - 1985 Oct. Venezuela, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 1985 Nov. 14-17, Hernando de Soto, Lima, Peru (Box 26)
  - 1985 Nov. 21-24, Social Science History Association, Chicago (Box 26)
  - 1985 Nov., "The New Institutional Economics in Historical Perspective" (Box 27)
  - 1985 Dec. 18-21, The World Bank: "Political Economy of Poverty, Equity, and Growth," Cancun, Mexico (Box 27)
  - 1985 Dec., Harvard Comments: "Ongoing Research on Institutional Change" (Box 27)
  - 1986 Jan. 30, University of California, San Diego (Box 27)
  - 1986 Feb. 11, James Roumasset Seminar on Tenure Choice, Washington University, St. Louis (Box 27)
  - 1986 Feb. 13-15, "Why International Rules, Norms, and Institutions Change," Harvard University (Box 27)
  - 1986 Spring, Murphy Institute (Box 27)
  - 1986 Mar. 21-23, Association for Asian Studies, Chicago (Box 27)
  - 1986 Mar. 27-28, "Historical Data and Theories of Rational Choice," Rutgers and Penn Talks (Box 27)
  - 1986 Mar., "The Origin of Modern Economic Growth" (Box 27)
  - 1986 Apr. 3, Economics, Southwest Missouri State (Box 27)
  - 1986 Apr. 8, "A Comment on Robert Tollison's 'Rent-Seeking.'" (Box 27)
  - 1986 Apr. 9, Towards a Freer Society (on Tullock), Liberty Fund, Williamsburg, Va. (Box 27)
  - 1986 Apr. 24, University of Montreal talk (Box 27)
  - 1986 May, Stockholm School of Economics (Box 27)
  - 1986 May 2-3, Carnegie Mellon Conference on Political Economy (Box 27)
  - 1986 May 6, Gary Becker - Workshop on Political Economy, Washington University, St. Louis (Box 27)
  - 1986 July 14-19, Liberty Fund Conference, Clemson, SC (Box 27)
  - 1986 Sept. 11-13, Liberty Fund Symposium, Center for the Study of American Business, Washington University, St. Louis (Box 27)
  - 1986 Sept. 17, The Path of Institutional Change, Luce Lecture, Washington University, St. Louis (Box 27)
  - 1986 Sept. 26-28, Economic History Association, Hartford, Conn. (Box 27)
  - 1986 Oct. 5-8, "On Friedman's Capitalism and Freedom," Symposium on Economic, Political, and Civil Freedom, Napa Valley, Calif. (Box 27)
  - 1986 Nov. 6-7, Northwest and Chicago (Box 27)
  - 1986 Nov. 7, Institutions, Economic Growth, and Freedom, Chicago workshop (Box 27)
  - 1986 Nov. 14-15, "Institutions and Economic Growth." Role of Institutions in Economic Development, Cornell University (Box 28)
  - 1986 Nov. 21-22, PERC/Liberty Fund colloquium: "The Moral and Ethical Basis for Economic Growth," Denver, Colo. (Box 28)
  - 1986 Dec. 28-30, Allied Social Science Associations Annual Meeting, New Orleans (Box 28)
  - 1986 AEA Conference: The New Political Economic History (Box 28)
  - 1987 Mar. 19-21, Conference on Political Economy and Business, Washington University, St. Louis (Box 28)
  - 1987 Apr. 8-11, Midwest Political Science Association Annual Meeting, Chicago (Box 28)
  - 1987 Apr. 23-26, Liberty Fund Symposium: Taxation, Democracy, and Threats to Liberty, Savannah, Ga. (Box 28)
  - 1987 June, Workshop on the Economics of Institutional Choice and Design, University of Economics, Vienna, Austria (Box 28)
  - 1987 Aug. - Sept., Unfree Labor conference, Memorial University of Newfoundland (Box 28)
  - 1987 Oct., Essay for The Rise of Merchant Empires conference (Box 28)
  - 1987 Oct., The Rise of Merchant Empires conference, University of Minnesota (Box 28)
  - 1987 Nov. 13-15, Conference on Knowledge and Institutional Change, University of Minnesota (Box 28)
  - 1988 June 8-10, New Institutional Economics Seminar (Box 28)
  - 1988 Oct. 12, Conference on Economic Development and the Law, Ramapo College, NJ (Box 28)
  - 1988 Oct. 21, Sequoia Institute (Box 28)
  - 1988 Oct. 21, Institutions of Democracy and Development Seminar (Box 28)
  - 1988 Oct. 24-25, Instituto Tecnologico Autonomo de Mexico (Box 29)
  - 1988 Nov. 2-5, History of Freedom Conference (Box 29)
  - 1988 Nov. 3, Columbia University talk (Box 29)
  - 1988 Nov. 5, American Academy of Arts and Sciences, Midwest Section, Chicago (Box 29)
  - 1988 Nov. 21, University of Illinois-Champaign talk (Box 29)
  - 1988 Dec. 28-30, AEA Meeting (Box 29)
  - 1989 Feb. 1-4, Towards a Scientific Analysis of Value, Tucson, Ariz. (Box 29)
  - 1989 Feb. 17, AID Conference: Informality and Economic Institutional Reform (Box 29)
  - 1989 Mar. 28-30, Lecture/Talk at Rice University (Box 29)
  - 1989 Apr. 20-23, "Liberty and the Economic Consequences of the French Revolution" (Box 29)
  - 1989 May 15-20, Liberty Fund Summer Series, University of Victoria (Box 29)
  - 1989 June 22, The Economic Role of the State, Amsterdam (Box 29)
  - 1989 June 24-27, The Second World Congress of Cliometrics (Box 29)
  - 1989 Aug. 21-25, Sweden Lectures (Box 29)
  - 1989 Sept. 14, Rochester (Box 29)
  - 1989 Sept. 15-16, "Government and Growth" (Box 29)
  - 1989 Oct. 23-27, Texas A and M, Kirby Distinguished Professorship (Box 29)
  - 1985 Nov., "The New Institutional Economics in Historical Perspective" (Box 30)
  - 1989 Nov. 3, Cornell Colloquium (Box 30)
  - 1989 Fall, Hernreich Chair in International Economics recruiting committee (Box 30)
  - 1990 Feb. 15, Yale Conference (Box 30)
  - 1990 Mar. 25-27, The Global Marketplace - National Conference of Editorial Writers, Washington University at St. Louis (Box 30)
  - 1990 Apr. 12-13, Ohio University lecture (Box 30)
  - 1990 Apr. 27-29, Revenue Extraction and the Institutionalization of the State, University of Washington (Box 30)
  - 1990 Oct. 12-13, Symposium: Capitalism and Social Progress, University of Virginia (Box 30)
  - 1990 Dec. 7, Washington Area Economic History Seminar (Box 30)
  - 1991 Jan. 30, University Lecture: The Unmaking of the Communist Revolution (Box 30)
  - 1991 Feb. 15, UCLA talk (Box 30)
  - 1991 Mar. 1-3, Fogel Conference: Strategic Factors in 19th Century U.S. Economic History (Box 30)
  - 1991 May 23-25, Political Economy Conference (Box 30)
  - 1991 June 16-19, IAREP/SASE Conference at Stockholm School of Economics (Box 30)
  - 1991 Sept. 9-10, [Conference on privatization], Kiel, Germany (Box 30)
  - 1991 Sept. 27-29, Economic History Association Annual Meeting - Boulder, Colo. (Box 30)
  - 1991 Nov. 8-10, Workshop on Institutional Theory in the Social Sciences (Box 30)
  - 1991 Nov. 14-15, Yale University Conference (Box 30)
  - 1991 Nov. 21, Dinner Talk Arts and Sciences Council on Soviet Union (Box 30)
  - 1991, World Bank - World Development Report (Box 31)
  - 1992 Jan. 3-5, AEA Meetings (Box 31)
  - 1992 Feb. 26-27, NSF Workshop on the Politics of Economic Reform in the Former Communist-Bloc States at UCLA, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - 1992 Mar. 6-8, African Conference (Box 31)
  - 1992 Mar. 10, Talk at UC Riverside (Box 31)
  - 1992 Mar. 12, Talk at Berkeley: A Transaction Cost Theory of Politics (Box 31)
  - 1992 Mar. 13-14, Conference: Credible Commitment and Institutions (Box 31)
  - 1992 Mar. 26, Talk - Eastern Europe Economies (Box 31)
  - 1992 Apr. 8-10, Explaining Economic Growth (Box 31)
  - 1992 June, 10th International Institutional Conference (Box 31)
  - 1992 Aug. 10, AFEA talk: Bellagio paper (Box 31)
  - 1992 Sept. 3-6, APSA Meeting - Round Table on Elinor Ostrom (Box 31)
  - 1992 Sept. 16-18, Evaluation of Emory University Economics Department (Box 31)
  - 1992 Oct. 17, talk to Executive Institute (Box 31)
  - 1992 Fall, Executive Institute: Global Connections and Conflict (Box 32)
  - 1992 Oct. 30, University of Illinois talks (Box 32)
  - 1992 Nov. 8-9, "The Role of Technology in Economics" (Box 32)
  - 1992 Dec. 4-5, Wallis Institute of Political Economy conference (Box 32)
  - 1993 Feb. 5, University of Pittsburgh (Box 32)
  - 1993 Feb. 5-6, Regulation, Institutions, and the Performance of Telecom Utilities (Box 32)
  - 1993 Mar. 19-21, The Public Choice Society Annual Meetings (Box 32)
  - 1993 Apr. 8-10, Cornell visit (Box 32)
  - 1993 May 23-27, World Productivity Congress, Stockholm (Box 32)
  - 1993 July 30-31, American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Social Capital and Economic Development workshop (Box 32)
  - 1993 Aug. 19-21, Arne Ryde Symposium on The Economic Analysis of Law (Box 32)
  - 1993 Sept. 17-19, "Third World Economic History/Development Group" - London (Box 32)
  - 1993 Sept. 16-18, World Bank Conference on Public Choice and Development, London (Box 32)
  - 1993 Oct. 1-3, The Economic History Association Fifty-Third Annual Meeting (Box 32)
  - 1993 Oct. 4-5, System Committee on International Economic Analysis, St. Louis (Box 32)
  - 1993 Oct. 17, The Second Economic Revolution, Samara/St. Louis Sister City Visit (Box 32)
  - 1993 Nov. 11-12, Workshop in Political Theory and Policy Analysis - Colloquium, Indiana University (Box 32)
  - 1993 Nov. 18-21, Rating Economic Freedom VI - Liberty Fund/Fraser Institute Colloquium, Sonoma, Calif. (Box 32)
  - 1993, Fundes (Box 32)
  - 1994 Feb. 18, World Bank Talk (Box 32)
  - 1994 Feb. 22, Economic Problems and Economic Analysis, Round Table, St. Louis (Box 32)
  - 1994 Mar. 17, UNC Political Economy Working Group, Chapel Hill (Box 32)
  - 1994 Mar. 25, USAID, Washington DC (Box 33)
  - 1994 Mar. 25, American Economic Association Nominating Committee Meeting, Washington DC (Box 33)
  - 1994 Apr. 1, UC San Diego (Box 33)
  - 1994 Apr. 14-15, John M. Olin Lecture Series, Lafayette College (Box 33)
  - 1994 Apr. 29, Rochester Institute of Technology, William D. Gasser Lectureship (Box 33)
  - 1994 May 2-3, Stockholm School of Economics (Box 33)
  - 1994 May 13-15, Conference on New Institutionalization in Economic Sociology, Cornell (Box 33)
  - 1994 May 16, Sunday Times Nobel Prizewinners Lecture Series, London (Box 33)
  - 1994 May 16-21, Dublin, Ireland (Box 33)
  - 1994 May 26, Transaction Cost Economics, Paris (Box 33)
  - 1994 June, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Box 33)
  - 1994 June 2-5, PERC Political Economy Forum: The Privatization Process, Montana (Box 33)
  - 1994 June 5-8, University of Washington, Seattle (Box 33)
  - 1994 June 22-23, Location Competition in the World Economy, Kiel Week Conference, Kiel, Germany (Box 33)
  - 1994 June 26-28, Premi de Economia, "Rey Jaime I," Valencia, Spain (Box 33)
  - 1994 Aug. 2-6, Visit to Brazil (Box 33)
  - 1994 Aug. 21-27, International Association for Research in Income and Wealth, St. Andrews, Canada (Box 33)
  - 1994 Sept. 12-17, International Congress of Economic History, Milan (Box 33)
  - 1994 Sept. 19, Scale and Scope in a Globalizing Environment, Graningen, Netherlands (Box 33)
  - 1994 Sept. 27, Adam Smith Lecture, National Association of Business Economists (Box 33)
  - 1994 Sept. 30 - Oct. 1, MacArthur Foundation Meeting, Chicago (Box 33)
  - 1994 Oct., Path Dependence, Columbia University (Box 33)
  - 1994 Oct. 6-8, Economic History Association, Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 33)
  - 1994 Oct. 13-16, Social Science History Association Meeting, Atlanta, Ga. (Box 34)
  - 1994 Oct. 14-15, "What Is Institutionalism Now?" University of Maryland, College Park (Box 34)
  - 1994 Oct. 25-26, Trinity University, San Antonio, Tex. (Box 34)
  - 1994 Oct. 28, "Institutions and Public Policy," St. Norbert College, Des Pere, Wis. (Box 34)
  - 1994 Nov. 21, Business History Seminar, Harvard University (Box 34)
  - 1994 Nov. 29, Dec. 5, Japan, Nobel Symposium (Box 34)
  - 1995 Jan., Methodology Session - AEA Meeting, Washington, DC (Box 34)
  - 1995 Jan. 6, AEA Meeting, Washington, DC (Box 34)
  - 1995 Feb. 3, Political Economy Lecture Series, Harvard University (Box 34)
  - 1995 Feb. 17, Texas A and M University Student Conference on National Affairs (Box 34)
  - 1995 Mar. 6-12, Chinese University of Hong Kong and Peking University, Beijing (Box 34)
  - 1995 Mar. 17-19, Frontiers of Economics, Washington University in St. Louis (Box 34)
  - 1995 Mar. 31, Apr. 1, Clemson University (Box 34)
  - 1995 Apr. 6, Economic Performance Through Time, Malim Harding Visitorship Lecture, University of Toronto (Box 34)
  - 1995 Apr. 21, Penn State Conference Series, University Park, Pa. (Box 34)
  - 1995 Apr. 27, Choate Rosemary Hall (Box 34)
  - 1995 May 24-28, IASCP World Conference, Bodo, Norway (Box 34)
  - 1995 May 29, Industrial Institute for Economic Research, Stockholm (Box 34)
  - 1995 June 21-24, Universidad Nacional Andres Bello, Santiago, Chile (Box 34)
  - 1995 June 26-27, Nobel Lecture: The Institutional Framework for Economic Development (Box 34)
  - 1995 June 25, July 1, Instituto Apoyo, Peru (Box 34)
  - 1995 Aug. 26, Sept. 1, Santa Fe Institute Conference (Box 34)
  - 1995 Oct. 4-6, St. Louis, Inaugural Symposium (Box 34)
  - 1995 Oct. 11, Departmental Seminar [Economics], UC Berkeley (Box 35)
  - 1995 Oct. 27-29, Economy of Early British America, Huntington Library, Calif. (Box 35)
  - 1995 Nov. 1, Stanford Workshop (Box 35)
  - 1995 Nov. 17-18, Institutional Framework and Economic Performance - OECD, Paris (Box 35)
  - 1996 Jan. 23, "Institutions, Technology, and Economic Growth" - talk at Stanford (Box 35)
  - 1996 Mar. 31, Apr. 2, Association of Private Enterprise Education, Las Vegas, Nev. (Box 35)
  - 1996 Apr. 3-4, UC Santa Barbara (lecture and visit) (Box 35)
  - 1996 Apr. 15, Austrian Economics Colloquium, New York University (Box 35)
  - 1996 Apr. 17, Henry George Lecture, St. John's University, Queens, NY (Box 35)
  - 1996 Apr. 22-24, UNC-Greensboro visit (Box 35)
  - 1996 Apr. 21-24, "Order, Disorder, and Economic Change," UNC-Greensboro visit (Box 35)
  - 1996 May 3, UCSD Colloquium on Political Reasoning (Box 35)
  - 1996 May 20-30, Judge Institute Visit, Cambridge University (Box 35)
  - 1996 June 2-5, Schumpeter Society Conference (Box 35)
  - 1996 June 20-22, Liberty Fund Conference on Property Rights (Box 35)
  - 1996 Aug. 7-9, "On the Conditions for Innovation and Growth" conference (Box 35)
  - 1996 Dec. 5-7, Kenan Institute, Duke Univ. workshop: Civil Society, Social Capital, and Development in Eurasia (Box 35)
  - 1997 Feb. Phi Beta Kappa" (Box 35)
  - 1997 Mar. 4-9, Helsinki UNO/WIDER conference (Box 35)
  - 1997 Mar. 20, Lecture at Queen's University (Box 35)
  - 1997 Mar., WIDER annual lectures delivered (Box 35)
  - 1997 Apr. 2, Lecture at University of Pennsylvania (Box 35)
  - 1997 Apr. 4, Lecture at University of Akron (Box 35)
  - 1997 Apr. 9-11, Lecture at TCU (Box 35)
  - 1997 Apr. Judicial Politics (Box 35)
  - 1997 June 13-14, Economic Growth and Market Institutions in Historical Perspective, Moscow (Box 35)
  - 1997 June 30, IFREE Organizational Meeting, Tucson, AZ (Box 36)
  - 1997 June, Italy, accepted invitations (Box 36)
  - 1997 Aug. 12, The Egyptian Center for Economic Study (Box 36)
  - 1997 Aug., APSA meeting (Box 36)
  - 1997 Aug., APSA meeting, Cognitive Science panel (Box 36)
  - 1997 Sept. 26, Lecture at Middlebury College (Box 36)
  - 1997 Sept., "Institutions and Productivity in History", Milan talk (Box 36)
  - 1997 Sept. Institutions conference (Box 36)
  - 1997 October 30, International EURO Symposium, St. Louis, MO (Box 36)
  - 1997 Nov. 1, American Academy of Arts and Sciences (103rd), Chicago (Box 36)
  - 1997 Nov. 13 - 19, Russel Sage Foundation, Nobelist Series, Univ. of Washington, Seattle (Box 36)
  - 1997 Nov. 14 - 17, Conference on the scientific study of judicial politics (Box 36)
  - 1997 Nov. 23 - 24, Latin America and the Caribbean Region Institutions, Organizations and Development Conference, Annapolis (Box 36)
  - 1997 Nov. 24, World Bank conference, Annapolis (Box 36)
  - 1997 Nov., La Scala - Milan conference (Box 36)
  - 1997 Dec. 4 - 6, Ten Nobels for the Future, Milan (Box 36)
  - 1997 Dec., "Beliefs, Institutions and the Process of Economic Change", Milan talk (Box 36)
  - 1997 Dec., Cairo (Box 36)
  - 1997, Pi Sigma Alpha and APSA meeting (Box 36)
  - 1997, Lecture at Widener (Box 36)
  - 1997, International Society for NIE (Box 36)
  - 1997-1999 ISNIE Schedules (Box 91)
  - 1997, APSA nobelists panel plenary meeting (Box 36)
    Includes a transcript of question and answer session with Douglass North, responses by James Buchanan.
  - 1998 Jan. - Mar., Hoover Institution, Stanford, CA (Box 36)
  - 1998 Jan. 3 - 5, AEA/ASSA meeting, Chicago, IL (Box 36)
  - 1998 Jan. 3 - 5, ASSA meeting, Chicago, IL (Box 36)
  - 1998 Jan. 23, Phoenix alumni talk, Phoenix, AZ (Box 36)
  - 1998 Jan. 24 - 25, IFREE board of directors meeting, Tucson, AZ (Box 36)
  - 1998 Jan. - Feb. Economic change workshop, Hoover, CA (Box 36)
  - 1998 Feb. 6 - 7, Norms and Evolution at the Grassroots of Asia workshop, The World Bank group, Stanford, CA (Box 36)
  - 1998 Feb. 18, Development seminar talk, Department of Economics, USC, Los Angeles, CA (Box 36)
  - 1998 Feb. 23, Faculty workshop, UCB, Berkeley, CA (Box 36)
  - 1998 Mar. 5, CATO Institute - luncheon, Washington D. C. (Box 36)
  - 1998 Mar. 11 - 13, Milken Institute conference, Los Angeles, CA (Box 36)
  - 1998 Mar. 19 - 21, MEA 62nd annual meeting, Chicago, IL (Box 37)
  - 1998 Mar. 26 - 29, 50th annual meeting of the Association for Asian Studies (Box 37)
  - 1998 Spring, Seminar on computer science and economics, Stanford, CA (Box 37)
  - 1998 Spring, Freshman research seminars, Washington University (Box 37)
  - 1998 Spring, University of Michigan (Box 37)
  - 1998 Mar. 30, Harvard/HIID/MIT growth and development seminar, Cambridge, MA (Box 37)
  - 1998 Apr. 7 - 11, World Bank water meeting, Rural Virginia (Box 37)
  - 1998 Apr. 8 - 10, Margaret Levi visit to Washington University (Box 37)
  - 1998 Apr. 17 - 19, Conference on experimental research on bargaining and learning, Washington University (Box 37)
  - 1998 Apr. 22, Lazarfeld Center workshop, Columbia University (Box 37)
  - 1998 Apr. 23, The Wall Street Journal breakfast, New York, NY (Box 37)
  - 1998 Apr. 26 - May 1, Advanced Institute for Federal Judges, George Mason University (Box 37)
  - 1998 May 8 - 9, ALEA meeting (after dinner speaker) (Box 37)
  - 1998 May 8 - 9, ALEA meeting (Oliver E. Williamson) (Box 37)
  - 1998 May 19 - 22, Seminar on Institutional Development and Economic Performance, Buenos Aires, Argentina (Box 37)
  - 1998 May. Doctorado Honoris Causa, Universidad de los Andes-Bogota. (Box 91)
  - 1998 June, Phi Beta Kappa society/The National Honor Society (Box 37)
  - 1998 June, Introductory note to "Big bang transformation of economic systems as a challenge to the new institutional economics," Saarbrucken, Germany (Box 37)
  - 1998 June 11 - 13, ESA annual meeting, Mannheim, Germany (Box 37)
  - 1998 July 2 - 4, Fondazione Rosselli: "Does Knowledge Matter to Politics?", Turin, Italy (Box 37)
  - 1998 Aug. 2 - 14, Tuebingen conference: "Research Strategies in New Institutional Economics", Washington University, St. Louis (Box 37)
  - 1998 Aug. 24, XII International economic history congress, Madrid, Spain (Box 37)
  - 1998 Sept., IFREE (General) (Box 37)
  - 1998 Oct., Faculty senate council lecture - Washington University Holmes lounge (Box 37)
  - 1998 Oct. 22 - 23, Toronto (Box 37)
  - 1998 Oct. 22 - 23, University of Toronto: Great Minds symposium, Toronto, Ontario (Box 37)
  - 1998 Oct. 27, World Bank meeting (Box 37)
  - 1998 Oct. 28, Eliot society tea, Washington University (Box 37)
  - 1998 Oct. 30, Ohio State University, Columbus, OH (Box 37)
  - 1998 Nov., Department of Information Systems lecture, UMBC (Box 38)
  - 1998 Nov. 11, Manhattanville College, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - 1998 Nov. 15, National Honor Society program (Box 38)
  - 1998 Nov. 17, Undergraduate Political Science Association faculty wine and cheese mixer (Box 38)
  - 1998 Nov. 24, Mary Institute/ St. Louis Country Day School (Box 38)
  - 1998 Dec. 1, Eliot Society talk (Box 38)
  - 1998 Dec. 2 - 3, Talk CIPE, Miami (Box 38)
  - 1998 Dec. 8, APSAN paper, part two (Box 38)
  - 1998 Dec. 12 - 13, Anthropological conference, Chicago (Box 38)
  - 1998 ISNIE (Box 91)
  - 1998 - 2000, ISNIE, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - 1999 Jan. 3 - 5, ASSA/AEA meeting, New York (Box 38)
  - 1999 Jan. 13, University of California, Davis (Box 38)
  - 1999 Jan. 18, Transaction Costs and Trust workshop, Palo Alto, CA, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - 1999 Feb. 5 - 6, World Bank: community markets (Box 38)
  - 1999 Feb: 5 -6, Douglass North's comments at Community and Markets in Economic Development workshop, Stanford University, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - 1999 Feb. 18 - 19, UNESCO water panel (Box 39)
  - 1999 Feb. 25, Social science history (Box 39)
  - 1999 Feb. 26 - 27, IFREE annual board meeting, Tucson, Arizona (Box 39)
  - 1999 Mar. 10 - 12, Milken Institute global conference, Beverly Hills, CA (Box 39)
  - 1999 Mar. 12, Milken conference - R. T. Nobel laureates (Box 39)
  - 1999 Mar. 25 - 26, Michigan State University (Box 39)
  - 1999 Mar. 25 - 26, "Dunaway Lecturer" Michigan State University East Lancing, MI (Box 39)
  - 1999 Mar., Ten Nobels for the Future, Milan (Box 39)
  - 1999 Spring, Global management course (Box 39)
  - 1999 Apr. 8 - 9, University of Kansas visit (Box 39)
  - 1999 Apr. 16 - 18, Decentralization conference, New York University (Box 39)
  - 1999 Apr. 19 - 22, Business Week awards, Erasmus University (Box 39)
  - 1999 Apr. 23 - 25, Cultural Values and Human Progress symposium, Cambridge (Box 39)
  - 1999 Apr. 28, "Economic Impact of Education System: Failure and Success", Common Ground Forum (Box 39)
  - 1999 Apr. 30 - May 1, Fourth Annual Colloquium on Environmental Law, Duke University, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - 1999 May, ISS lecture (Box 39)
  - 1999 May, 12 - 14, CLSA China forum, Beijing (Box 39)
  - 1999 May 6 - 9, F. A. Hayek's 100th birthday, University of Freiburg, Germany, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - 1999 May 13 - 14, Dubrovmik symposium, Stanford University (Box 39)
  - 1999 May 21 - 22, Henry Manne conference, Williamsburg, VA (Box 39)
  - 1999 May 27 - 29, "Enterprise in Transition" conference, University of Split, Croatia (Box 39)
  - 1999 May 28 - 30, Historical Society, Boston University (Box 39)
  - 1999 May 28 - 29, Berlin internet economics workshop (Box 39)